allpropertymanagement.com 2011-11-29

# AllPropertyManagement.com - Rental and Association Management Companies

## TERMS OF USE

The allpropertymanagement.com web site is in intended for use by prospective property management clients only.

Any commercial use of the data, content, text, or images contained in the web site or its database is strictly prohibited and constitutes and infringement of our copyrighted work and content.

* * *

## PRIVACY POLICY

All Property Management, LLC [has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with TRUSTe's program requirements including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions.](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) This privacy statement covers the Web site [www.allpropertymanagement.com](http://www.allpropertymanagement.com/).

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact us at 888-238-8948. [If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact TRUSTe here.](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint)

### General Information

All Property Management, LLC respects the privacy of visitors to our online site. Any personal information gathered on this site will be kept strictly confidential and will only be used in ways for which you have specifically consented. We will never sell or rent any personal information collected from you to any third party. We will take special care to protect the privacy and security of your information.

All Personally Identified Information gathered on this website is in accordance with the Privacy Policy.

### Privacy Contact Information

You can contact All Property Management regarding privacy matters by mail at

All Property Management  
2505 3rd Avenue, Suite 325  
Seattle, WA 98121

Or by email by using our [Contact Form by clicking here](http://www.allpropertymanagement.com/contact/)

### Collection and Use of Personally Identifiable Information

All Property Management, LLC will only collect personally identifiable data, such as your name, home address, rental property address, telephone number, or e-mail address, when it is voluntarily submitted to us at this website. This information will be collected through our online "Get A Quote" form.

No other third parties, either on our behalf or for themselves, other than the property management companies you select, will collect any Personally Identified Information through this website.

Should you need to correct or update your personal information, you may do so by emailing us by using our [Contact Form by clicking here](http://www.allpropertymanagement.com/contact/). [We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at 888-238-8948. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html)

* * *

## TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES

### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

This website also collects and uses information in aggregate form to track the total number of visitors to our site, the number of visitors to each page of our site, the domain names of our visitors' Internet service providers, and other such technical information. This is technical information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. No personally identifiable information is available in this process and referred to as "non-personally identifiable information". We use this data to better target our marketing efforts.

### Cookies

Our website uses a technology called "cookies". A cookie is a token that a server gives to your browser when you access a website. Cookies are capable of storing many types of data. Cookies help provide additional functionality to the site or to help us analyze site usage more accurately. In all cases in which cookies are used, the cookie will not collect personally identifiable information except with your explicit permission. We do not, however, use cookies to track the navigational habits of identified visitors. We do use Google Analytics to track aggregate data for our site.

[Our third party Live-chat service provider uses cookies to help us provide better customer service. We do not have access or control over these cookies, nor are they covered by this privacy policy.](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) In all cases in which cookies are used, the cookie will not collect personally identifiable information except with your explicit permission.

### Change of Privacy Policy

If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection through this Web site, we will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already collected through our site, we will post a prominent notice on our web site [prior to the changes taking effect.](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html)

### Security

We take careful measures to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of your information. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology supporting 128-bit encryption when we collect information from you. The information collected is stored on secure servers behind a firewall. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. We only provide access to your personal information to All Property Management, LLC employees and the companies from which you request information.

### Disclosure of Information

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

### Testimonials

We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer's name. We do obtain the customer's consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial.

### Blog

If you use a bulletin board, blog, or chat room on this Web site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. [To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at 888-238-8948. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html)

### Third Party Links

As a convenience to our visitors, allpropertymanagement.com currently contains links to a number of sites that we believe may offer useful information. The privacy policies and procedures described here do not apply to those sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their data collection and distribution policies.

We do not allow third party advertisers to track your browsing.

### Change in Ownership

If All Property Management is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

* * *

## INFORMATION DISCLAIMER

All Property Management tries to provide content that is true and accurate as of the date of writing; however, we give no assurance or warranty regarding the accuracy, timeliness, or applicability of any of the contents. Visitors to allpropertymanagement.com web site should confirm with the appropriate state real estate commission or licensing agency that a property manager has the appropriate licensing and credentials. If you have any questions regarding how to reach the appropriate real estate commission or licensing agency please contact us at 888-238-8948.

The information at allpropertymanagement.com does not in any way constitute legal or professional advice and is not intended to take the place of either the written law or regulations. All Property Management, LLC, its owners, directors and other representatives cannot be held liable for actions and will not be liable for damages or losses arising from the use of such information.

All Property Management does not advocate or endorse the engagement or use of any particular property management company. Selection and arrangements with any given company are the responsibility of the service user.

All Property Management  
2505 3rd Avenue, Suite 325  
Seattle, WA 98121
